https://www.surfpm.com/privacy-policy

Bases
Etc.
Gloves
Etc.
Bases
Etc.
Gloves
Etc.
Privacy Policy
-  Surfpm.com is strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with our content, products and services. We want to provide a safe and secure environment for you and your children.
- Information is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. It is entirely your choice whether to respond to these questions or not.
- Surfpm.com collects two types of information. The first type is anonymous information. For instance, we may collect information to tell us that five thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth - they are 'anonymous' to us.
- The second type of information that Surfpm.com collects is personal information. Surfpm.com will collect personal information that lets us know the specifics of who you are such as your name, email address, or postal address when you provide it to us. With this information, Surfpm.com can provide a variety of personalized and enhanced services that are not available to anonymous users. We hope that you will find it beneficial to provide individually identifiable information about yourself to us because it will make our services more valuable to you.
- Sometimes, we may specifically ask for personal information about you when you sign up to use a service. Certain information may be required, such as your name, age, internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer or credit card number in order to provide that service or product to you. This information may also be used to inform you of additional products and services which may interest you. You can choose not to receive such information when you are undertaking product or service registration on our website.
- Surfpm.com automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor the use of Surfpm.com like the numbers and frequency of visitors to Surfpm.com and its areas. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve Surfpm.com to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many users as possible. Surfpm.com may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.
- Surfpm.com will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. Surfpm.com will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.
- There will be occasions where it will be necessary for Surfpm.com to disclose your personal information to third parties. Surfpm.com may be required by law to disclose the information, or Surfpm.com may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested, for example, if you purchase products online, Surfpm.com will need to disclose your personal information to third parties in order to bill and deliver your products. However, the disclosure will only be made where it is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information. Otherwise than stated above, we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number to any organization or person outside Surfpm.com unless you have authorized us to do so.
No sale of personal information: Under no circumstances Surfpm.com will sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.
- Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any personal information. Be responsible whenever you are online.
- Surfpm.com operates secure data networks that are designed to protect your privacy and security.
Complaints about privacy:
If you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on our websites, please notify Surfpm.com. While Surfpm.com accepts no liability for any material or links posted to the service, we will investigate all complaints.
Changes to Surfpm.com privacy policy:
If we decide to change the Surfpm.com Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here
Continue
